

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Phone: +54 387 5185752 Email: crgiodm@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergio-

david-full-stack

GitHub: https://github.com/sergiodm92

Portfolio: sergiodm.online

# **SERGIO DAVID**

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER -CIVIL ENGINEER

### **EDUCATION**

### Civil Engineer - Self-taught

#### Full Stack Web Developer

Tecnologías: • JavaScript

- Python
- React
- React-Query
- Material UI
- Express
- fastAPI
- HTML5.
- Express
- MongoDB

Next.js

TypeScript

- Redux
- Bootstrap
- CSS3
- · Nest.is
- Node.js · Postgre SQL.
- Firebase

English Level: Intermediate

Agile Methodologies: Scrum, Trello

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a highly proactive individual with a passion for continuous learning and self-improvement. I adapt quickly to changes and have extensive experience in solving complex problems, enabling me to approach challenging projects with a positive attitude and an open mindset. My experience in web development has allowed me to gain strong technical knowledge and practical skills in managing web projects from start to finish. Furthermore, I have developed the ability to work effectively in multidisciplinary teams and in organizing tasks and efficient work processes..

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Full Stack Developer 05/2023- 12/2023

#### VinciBlock (Remote) **Full Stack**

• Front-End Development (React-Redux Toolkit, ReactQuery, Next.js, TypeScript) Responsive Design / Back-End Development (Node.js, TypeScript, Nest.js), Database (MongoDB). • Team Leader, Front-End Development for BussinesShop project (https://www.businessshop.ai/) and Monbasa Landing (https://www.monbasacantera.com/)

#### Front-End Developer 03/2023- 05/2023

#### Branak (Remote) **Full Stack**

 Front-End Development (React-Redux) Responsive Design / Back-End Development (Node.js, GraphQL, socket.io), Database (NoSQL DynamoDB, AWS).

#### Full Stack Developer 08/2022- 03/2023

#### GlobalLogic (Remote) **Full Stack Junior**

 Team Development using Jira-GitFlow, SCRUM. / Front-End Development (React-Redux and Next.js) Responsive Design / Back-End Development (Node.js and FastAPI), Database (MongoDB).

# **FREELANCE**

#### Back-End Developer 05/2022-08/2023

Management Software for Instituto del Norte (Salta, Argentina)

• Full Back-End Development (Python-FastAPI), database (Firebase). • Collaboration in Front-End Development (React-Next.js-TypeScript).

#### Full Stack Developer 10/2022-02/2023

Don Alberto Meats (Catamarca, Argentina) (In a team using agile methodologies)

• System Development / Mockup, UX Design for Client Presentation / Front-end Development (React-Redux) Responsive Design / Back-end Development (Node.js-Express), Database (Firebase).

#### Full Stack Developer 03/2022-04/2023

#### **Creation of Invitation Cards for Events**

- Full Back-End Development (Python-FastAPI), Database (Firebase).
- Collaboration in Front-End Development (React-Next.js-TypeScript).